A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A93), 1985-1993; 1.19; 121.03 Cubic Feet; 274 letter size document boxes and 1 legal size document box; Boxes 1-275
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - RF 89034 A124 - Kehinde, Lucy A., 1988-1993, 1996-1997 (Box 164, Folder 1001)
      African Dissertation Internship Award - Dissertation topic: "The Influence of Extension and Other Information Sources on the Adoption of a New Technology: A Study of the Adoption of Soybean Production Technology and Utilization Among Small-Scale Farmers in South Western Nigeria"
    - RF 89034 A124 - Kehinde, Lucy A., 1988-1993, 1996-1997 (Box 164, Folder 1001A)
    - RF 89034 A137 - Akin-Olugbade, Adesegun A., 1989-1992, 1997 (Box 164, Folder 1002-1003, Box 165, Folder 1004)
      African Dissertation Internship Award - Dissertation topic: "Feasibility of Region Wide Banking in West Africa: Comparative Analysis of Laws and Regulations Governing the Entry and Operations of Banks in Anglophone and Francophone West Africa"
    - RF 89035 A1 - International Center for Bantu Civilizations - African Art Exhibit, 1989-1990, 1997 (Box 165, Folder 1005)
    - RF 89035 A1 - International Center for Bantu Civilizations - African Art Exhibit: Supplementary Material (Box 165, Folder 1006)
    - RF 89035 A4 - Brooklyn Museum - "Facing History" Exhibit, 1989-1991 (Box 165, Folder 1007)
      "Facing History: The Black Image in American Art"
    - RF 89035 A5 - Smithsonian Institution - Caribbean Festivals Exhibit, 1988-1990 (Box 165, Folder 1008)
    - RF 89035 A6 - Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe - "Revered Earth" Exhibition, 1988-1991 (Box 165, Folder 1009, Box 166, Folder 1010)
    - RF 89035 A7 - University of Arizona - Tribal Museums Assessment, 1989-1991 (Box 166, Folder 1011)
    - RF 89035 A8 - Studio Museum in Harlem - African Art Exhibition, 1987-1991 (Box 166, Folder 1012-1013)
    - RF 89035 A9 - Washington Project for the Arts, Inc. - "The Blues Aesthetic: Black Culture and Modernism", 1987-1991 (Box 166, Folder 1014, Box 167, Folder 1015)
    - RF 89035 A9 - Washington Project for the Arts, Inc. - "The Blues Aesthetic: Black Culture and Modernism": Supplementary Material (Box 167, Folder 1016)
    - RF 89037 A47 - Hallwalls, Inc. - Interdisciplinary Artists, 1986-1990, 1993 (Box 167, Folder 1017)
    - RF 89040 A2 - Corporation for the Advancement of Policy Evaluation - Implementation Activities for Child Care Plus, 1989-1990 (Box 167, Folder 1018)
    - RF 89041 - Public/Private Ventures - California Conservation Corps, 1989-1993 (Box 167, Folder 1019-1020)
    - RF 89055 A38 - Tutwiler, Richard Neel, 1987-1992 (Box 168, Folder 1021)
      File also contains information on Lawrence C. Becker - West Africa Rice Development Association (WARDA)
      Grant administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), Aleppo, Syria
    - RF 89055 A38 - Tutwiler, Richard Neel, 1987-1992 (Box 168, Folder 1021A)
    - RF 89055 A39 - Renkow, Mitchell Adam, 1987-1992 (Box 168, Folder 1022-1023)
      Grant administered by Rockefeller Foundation and Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT), Mexico City, Mexico
    - RF 89055 A39 - Renkow, Mitchell Adam, 1987-1992 (Box 168, Folder 1022A)
    - RF 89055 A40 - Adesina, Akinwumi Ayodeji, 1987-1994, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 1024-1025, Box 169, Folder 1026-1027)
      Grant administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT), Hyderabad, India
    - RF 89055 A40 - Adesina, Akinwumi Ayodeji, 1987-1994, 1997 (Box 168, Folder 1024A)
    - RF 89055 A43 - Williams, Timothy Olalekan, 1986-1991 (Box 169, Folder 1028)
      Grant administered by Rockefeller Foundation and International Livestock Centre for Africa (ILCA), Addis Ababa, Ethiopia
    - RF 89055 A43 - Williams, Timothy Olalekan, 1986-1991 (Box 169, Folder 1028A)
    - RF 89057 A112 - Hu, Mengdong, 1985-1991 (Box 169, Folder 1029)
    - RF 89058 A15 - University of Quebec - Rabies Vaccine Research, 1987-1990, 1997 (Box 169, Folder 1030)
    - RF 89067 A40 - Electronic Arts Intermix - "Building Bridges: Cooperative Strategies for the 90's" Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 170, Folder 1031)
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects, 1986-1992, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 1032-1035, Box 171, Folder 1036-1037)
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box 171, Folder 1038-1039)
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-1, 6-22-89, Montpelier Room, 8:30 AM
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-2, 6-22-89, Sagamore Hill, 10:15 AM
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-3, 6-22-89, Sagamore Hill Room
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-4, 6-22-89, Ballroom Center, 12 PM
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-5, 6-23-89, Sagamore Hill, Sides 1 and 2
    - RF 89069 A27 - San Antonio Cares - Persistent Poverty Projects: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audio cassette tape: T-6, 6-23-89, Sagamore Hill, Side 3
    - RF 89073 A7 - Comerization - Video Production and Distribution, 1989-1991 (Box 171, Folder 1040, Box 172, Folder 1041)
    - RF 89081 - Connecticut College - Fellowships for Foreign Language Teachers in the High Schools, 1984-1997 (Box 172, Folder 1042-1044, Box 173, Folder 1045-1049, Box 174, Folder 1050-1054, Box 175, Folder 1055-1056)
    - RF 89081 - Connecticut College - Fellowships for Foreign Language Teachers in the High Schools: Supplementary Material (Box 175, Folder 1057-1058)
    - RF 89081 - Connecticut College - Fellowships for Foreign Language Teachers in the High Schools: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Ampex Reel-to-Reel Tape #671/2400', box dated 12/3/82
    - RF 89089 - Harvard University - Health Research for Developing Countries, 1986-1991 (Box 175, Folder 1059, Box 176, Folder 1060-1062)
    - RF 89090 A3 -HeaIth Transition Task Force - Donor's Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 1063)
    - RF 89090 A4 - Health Transition - Workshops, 1989-1990 (Box 176, Folder 1064)
    - RF 89090 A4 - Health Transition - Workshops: Supplementary Material (Box 176, Folder 1065, Box 177, Folder 1066-1070)
    - RF 89091 A53 - Centro de Pesquisa e Assistencia em Reproducao Humana - Single Contraceptive Implant Study Coordination, 1990-1992 (Box 177, Folder 1071)
    - RF 89096 A6 - Soils Research in Africa, 1989-1991 (Box 178, Folder 1072)
    - RF 89101 A7 - Workshop on Popularisation of Science and Technology in West Africa, 1990-1991 (Box 178, Folder 1073)
    - RF 90001 A2 - Alternate ROOTS, Inc. - Southeastern Artists Performances, 1989-1991 (Box 274, Folder 1693)
      ROOTS - Regional Organization of Theatres South
    - RF 90001 A4 - East Tennessee Foundation - Knoxville World Festival, 1989-1990, 1993 (Box 274, Folder 1694)
    - RF 90001 A6 - National Black Arts Festival (Atlanta) - 1990 International Programs, 1989-1991 (Box 274, Folder 1695-1696)
    - RF 90001 A7 - Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival, Inc. - International Dance, 1987-1992 (Box 275, Folder 1697-1700)
    - RF 90001 A8 - Pregones Touring Puerto Rican Theater Collection, Inc. - 1990 Teatro Festival, 1990-1991 (Box 275, Folder 1701)
    - RF 90001 A9 - Movement Theatre International, 1989-1991 (Box 275, Folder 1702)
    - RF 90001 A11 - Friends of the Arts, Inc. - Forum on the American Aesthetic, 1989-1993 (Box 275, Folder 1703)
    - RF 90001 A12 - Los Angeles Festival - International Artists Expenses and Conference Activities, 1988-1993 (Box 178, Folder 1074-1076)
    - RF 90001 A12 - Los Angeles Festival - International Artists Expenses and Conference Activities: Supplementary Material (Box 178, Folder 1077)
    - RF 90002 - "Arts of Mexico'' Exhibition - Educational and Performing Arts Programs in Host Cities, 1990-1992 (Box 179, Folder 1078-1079)
    - RF 90002 - "Arts of Mexico'' Exhibition - Educational and Performing Arts Programs in Host Cities: Supplementary Material (Box 179, Folder 1080)
    - RF 90002 A1 - Hostos Community College Advisory Council, Inc. - Mexican Art and Music, 1989-1991 (Box 179, Folder 1081)
    - RF 90002 A3 - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Scholarly Symposia on Mexican Art, 1987-1992 (Box 180, Folder 1082-1086)
    - RF 90002 A4 - Americas Society, Inc. - Mexican Literature, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 1087)
    - RF 90002 A5 - City College of the City University of New York - Latin American Book Fair and Mexico Exhibit, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 181, Folder 1088)
    - RF 90002 A6 - New York Shakespeare Festival (Public Theatre) - "Romeo y Julieta" from Mexico, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 1089)
    - RF 90002 A7 - International Center of Photography - "Between Worlds: Contemporary Mexican Photography" Exhibition, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 1090)
    - RF 90002 A8 - Texas Committee for the Humanities - Outreach with San Antonio Public Library Foundation, 1989-1992 (Box 181, Folder 1091-1093)
    - RF 90002 A9 - Museo del Barrio - "Through the Path of Echoes: Contemporary Art in Mexico" Exhibition, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 181, Folder 1094)
    - RF 90002 A10 - Mexican Cultural Achievements Exhibition, 1987-1991, 1997 (Box 182, Folder 1095-1097)
    - RF 90002 A10 - Mexican Cultural Achievements Exhibition: Supplementary Material (Box 182, Folder 1098-1099)
    - RF 90002 A11 - University of Mexico Permanent Extension School (San Antonio) - "Mexico: Splendors of Thirty Centuries" Exhibit Lecture Series, 1989-1991 (Box 183, Folder 1100)
    - RF 90002 A12 - Instituto Cultural Mexicano (Texas) - "The History of Mexican Textiles" Exhibit, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 1101)
    - RF 90002 A13 - University of Texas (San Antonio) - Arts of the Southwest and Mexico, 1989-1992 (Box 183, Folder 1102)
    - RF 90002 A14 - Mexico - Mexican Music in New York, 1990, 1994 (Box 183, Folder 1103)
    - RF 90002 A15 - Plaza de la Raza - Margo Albert Festival of the Arts, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 1104)
    - RF 90002 A16 - (The) Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center - Chicano Art/Mexican Art Exhibition and Chicano Media Arts Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 183, Folder 1105)
    - RF 90002 A17 - Self-Help Graphics and Art, Inc. - "The Arts of Mexico - Its North American Variant", 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 1106)
    - RF 90002 A18 - Tonantzin - Traditional Mexican Dance, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 1107)
    - RF 90003 A454 - University of Maryland - "Environmental Ethics: Survey and Assessment" Research Project, 1990, 1993-1994 (Box 183, Folder 1108)
    - RF 90003 A458 - Hunter College - International Interdisciplinary Congress on Women, 1988-1990 (Box 184, Folder 1109-1110)
    - RF 90003 A462 - Fellowships - Humanities - Humanistic Perspectives on Environmental Concerns, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 184, Folder 1111)
    - RF 90003 A469 - University of Hawaii - Resident Fellows, 1988-1992, 1995 (Box 184, Folder 1112, Box 185, Folder 1113)
    - RF 90003 A469 - University of Hawaii - Resident Fellows: Supplementary Material (Box 185, Folder 1114-1115)
    - RF 90003 A472 - (The) Newberry Library - Native American Tales on Film, 1989-1991, 1993 (Box 185, Folder 1116)
    - RF 90003 A473 - University of Houston - Conferences on Restoring Hispanic Literary Heritage of the U.S., 1989-1992, 1996 (Box 186, Folder 1117)
    - RF 90003 A474 - Cornell University - "Ethical Guidelines for Global Bargains" Study, 1990-1991, 1996 (Box 186, Folder 1118)
    - RF 90003 A475 - University of California, Santa Cruz - "Cultural Politics and Contemporary Social Movements" Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 186, Folder 1119)
    - RF 90004 A59 - Bryn Mawr College - CHART (Collaboratives for Humanities and Arts Teaching) Conferences on Curricular Change, 1990-1991 (Box 186, Folder 1120)
    - RF 90004 A71 - Community Foundation of Greater Washington, Inc. - Superintendent's Academy for Humanities and Arts Teaching, 1989-1991 (Box 186, Folder 1121-1122)
    - RF 90004 A73 - Network for Secondary Schools - Announcement of the New Mexico CHART (Collaboratives for Humanities and Arts Teaching) Initiative, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 1123)
    - RF 90005 A13 - (The) Studio Museum in Harlem "Five Artists from Contemporary Africa" Exhibition, 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 187, Folder 1124)
    - RF 90005 A14 - University of Texas, Austin - "The School of the South: The Torres-Garcia Workshop (1934-1962)" Exhibition, 1989-1991 (Box 187, Folder 1125)
    - RF 90005 A15 - Museum of Photographic Arts - "Revelaciones: The Photographs of Manuel Alvarez Bravo" Traveling Exhibition, 1989-1992 (Box 187, Folder 1126-1127)
    - RF 90005 A15 - Museum of Photographic Arts - "Revelaciones: The Photographs of Manuel Alvarez Bravo" Traveling Exhibition (Box T5)
      ¾" Videocassette – "Revelaciones: The Art of Manuel Alvarez Bravo" – A Museum of Photographic Arts Presentation - Robert Schneider, Producer, Isaac Artenstein, Director – 16:15 minutes, Mixed Track 9-14-90, Copyright MoPA 1990
    - RF 90005 A19 - Institute of International Education - Conference on International Exhibitions, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 1128)
    - RF 90005 A22 - (The) Brooklyn Museum - "Caribbean Festival Arts" Exhibition, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 1129)
    - RF 90005 A24 - (The) Children's Museum, Boston - Multicultural Professional Development Project, 1989-1993 (Box 187, Folder 1130, Box 188, Folder 1131)
    - RF 90005 A25 - Afro-American Historical and Cultural Museum - "Contemporary African Artists: Changing Tradition" Exhibition, 1990-1991, 1993 (Box 188, Folder 1132)
    - RF 90005 A26 - Crocker Art Museum Association - Mexican Art and Culture Programs, 1990-1991 (Box 188, Folder 1133)
    - RF 90005 A27 - Studio Museum in Harlem - "The Decade Show: Frameworks of Identity in the 1980s", 1988-1991 (Box 188, Folder 1134-1135)
      Collaborative project of The Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art, The New Museum of Contemporary Art, and The Studio Museum in Harlem
    - RF 90005 A27 - Studio Museum in Harlem - "The Decade Show: Frameworks of Identity in the 1980s": Supplementary Material (Box 188, Folder 1136-1137)
    - RF 90005 A28 - Social and Public Art Resource Center - "World Wall: A Vision of the Future Without Fear" Exhibition, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 189, Folder 1138)
    - RF 90007 - (The) Urban Institute - Employment Discrimination on the Basis of Race, 1987-1988, 1990-1993 (Box 189, Folder 1139-1142)
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development, 1987-1993, 1995-1996, 2001 (Box 189, Folder 1143, Box 190, Folder 1144-1146)
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development (Box 190, Folder 1145)
      Maxell 5.25" floppy disk
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development: Supplementary Material (Box 190, Folder 1147-1148, Box 191, Folder 1149-1153)
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audiocassette tape - Wye External Programme - Agricultural Economics for Development: Bands 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audiocassette tape - Wye External Programme - Economic and Social Survey Methods and Data Analysis: Bands 1, 2, 3, 4, 5
    - RF 90019 - Wye College of the University of London - External Studies Program in Agricultural Development: Supplementary Material (Box T5)
      Audiocassette - Wye External Programme - Economic and Social Survey Methods and Data Analysis: Band 6
    - RF 90021 - Friends of the Institute for a Democratic Alternative for South Africa, 1988-1995 (Box 192, Folder 1154-1159)
    - RF 90021 A4 - Friends of the Institute for a Democratic Alternative for South Africa - Media and South Africa Conference, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box 193, Folder 1160)
    - RF 90027 A4 - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases - Workshop on Use of Intelligent Geographic Information Systems, 1990-1993, 1995 (Box 193, Folder 1161)
    - RF 90027 A6 - International Council for Research in Agroforestry - Soil Fertility Improvement, 1991-1993 (Box 193, Folder 1162)
    - RF 90027 A8 - Overseas Development Institute - Environmental Management in Kenya, 1990-1993, 1996 (Box 193, Folder 1163)
    - RF 90028 - International Laboratory for Research on Animal Diseases - Vaccine Impact Studies, 1985-1992 (Box 193, Folder 1164-1166, Box 194, Folder 1167-1168)
    - RF 90029 - Malawi - Ministry of Agriculture - Soybean Research, 1989-1992, 1996 (Box 194, Folder 1169-1172, Box 195, Folder 1173)
    - RF 90031 A106 - Louisiana State University - Somaclonal Variation in Rice, 1988-1991, 1996 (Box 195, Folder 1174-1175)
    - RF 90031 A115 - Hokkaido University - Genetic Transformation of Rice, 1988-1990, 1997 (Box 195, Folder 1176)
    - RF 90031 A115 - Hokkaido University - Genetic Transformation of Rice: Supplementary Material (Box 195, Folder 1177)
    - RF 90031 A124 - University of California, Davis - Genetic Transformation of Rice, 1987-1993 (Box 196, Folder 1178-1179)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 8505 - Florida Justice Institute - National IOLTA (Interest on Lawyers' Trust Accounts) Clearinghouse, 1983-1989 (Box 196, Folder 1180-1182)
    - EO 8505 - Florida Justice Institute - National IOLTA (Interest on Lawyers' Trust Accounts) Clearinghouse: Supplementary Material (Box 196, Folder 1183, Box 197, Folder 1184-1185)
    - EO 8520 - University of Michigan - Sex Roles and Women's Earnings, 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1186)
      Study entitled "Sex Role Socialization, Labor Market Segregation and Women's Earnings"
    - EO 8521 - New York University - Women and Affirmative Action, 1985-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 197, Folder 1187)
      Study entitled "Unintended Consequences of Affirmative Action Programs: Some Emerging Problems for Working Women"
    - EO 8543 - Yale University - Gender and Legal Education, 1985-1991 (Box 198, Folder 1188)
      Study entitled "Gender and Professional Socialization Issues in Law and Legal Education"
    - EO 8543 - Yale University - Gender and Legal Education: Supplementary Material (Box 198, Folder 1189)
    - EO 8704 - Children's Village - Work Appreciation for Youth Program, 1986-1988, 1990, 1996 (Box 198, Folder 1190)
    - EO 8728 - Impacts of Employment and Training Programs on Disadvantaged Persons, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 1191-1192)
    - EO 8729 - Stanford University - Disadvantaged Students Education Conference, 1986-1990 (Box 199, Folder 1193-1194)
    - EO 8743 - University of Michigan - Census Tract Information, 1987-1991 (Box 199, Folder 1195-1196)
    - EO 8744 - National League of Cities Institute, Inc. - Children and Families in Cities Project, 1986-1991 (Box 199, Folder 1197, Box 200, Folder 1198-1201)
    - EO 8744 - National League of Cities Institute, Inc. - Children and Families in Cities Project: Supplementary Material (Box 200, Folder 1202, Box 201, Folder 1203-1204)
    - EO 8802 - Enterprise Foundation - Baltimore Middle East Neighborhood, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 201, Folder 1205-1206)
    - EO 8803 - University of California, Los Angeles - Program Retention, 1985-1988, 1990-1991 (Box 201, Folder 1207, Box 202, Folder 1208-1212)
    - EO 8809 - Women's Research and Education Institute - Family Leave Policy Papers, 1987-1991 (Box 202, Folder 1213)
    - EO 8814 - Catholic University of America, Washington, D.C. - "Washington Latinos at the Crossroads: A Study of Youths at Risk for Persistent Poverty", 1987-1992 (Box 203, Folder 1214-1215)
    - EO 8815 - University of California, Los Angeles - AIDS Epidemic and Crime, 1987-1990, 1992 (Box 203, Folder 1216)
    - EO 8817 - Council of Chief State School Officers - At-Risk Students, 1986-1989 (Box 203, Folder 1217-1218)
    - EO 8823 - Parikh, Sunita A., 1988, 1991 (Box 203, Folder 1219)
      Study of preference policies devised to promote the socioeconomic mobility of blacks in the U.S. and the untouchables of India
    - EO 8825 - Hispanic Policy Development Project - High School and Beyond Survey, 1987-1991 (Box 204, Folder 1220-1223)
    - EO 8834 - Public/Private Ventures - Summer Training and Education Program (STEP), 1987-1992 (Box 204, Folder 1224-1225, Box 205, Folder 1226-1227)
    - EO 8844 - Cornell University - Urban Economy and the Persistently Poor, 1988-1990 (Box 205, Folder 1228)
    - EO 8846 - University of Massachusetts - Low Income Mothers, 1988, 1992 (Box 205, Folder 1229)
      Study title: "Child Care Dilemmas and Coping Strategies Among Low-Income Mothers"
    - EO 8847 - Rand Corporation - Illegal Economic Activities in Washington, D.C., 1986-1996 (Box 205, Folder 1230-1231, Box 206, Folder 1232-1234)
      Study of "the role of illegal activities in the economic life of the underclass in Washington, D.C."
    - EO 8847 - Rand Corporation - Illegal Economic Activities in Washington, D.C.: Supplementary Material (Box 206, Folder 1235-1237, Box 207, Folder 1238-1239)
    - EO 8852 - Community Planning and Action - Coordination, 1988-1991, 1996-1997 (Box 207, Folder 1240-1241)
    - EO 8853 - Trends, Inc. - Fair Housing Check-Ups, 1987-1991 (Box 207, Folder 1242, Box 208, Folder 1243)
    - EO 8855 - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research - Children's Issues, 1988-1990 (Box 208, Folder 1244)
      Series of papers for a convening entitled "Seminar on Children's Issues for New Executive Branch Appointees"
    - EO 8891 - Southport Institute of Policy Analysis - Adult Literacy, 1988-1990, 1992 (Box 208, Folder 1245-1246)
    - EO 8902 - Federal City Council - Washington D.C. Public School System Review, 1984-1990 (Box 208, Folder 1247, Box 209, Folder 1248-1250)
    - EO 8903 - New School for Social Research - Community-Based Economic Development, 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 1251-1253, Box 210, Folder 1254)
    - EO 8904 - Southern Education Foundation - Public Policy and Education Conference, 1988-1990, 1992, 1995 (Box 210, Folder 1255-1256)
    - EO 8905 - Joint Center For Political Studies - Inner City Youth Documentary, 1988-1991 (Box 210, Folder 1257)
      Documentary title: "Turning It Around: Urban Teens in Crisis"
    - EO 8910 - Ontario Social Development Council - Self-Employment Issues, 1989-1991 (Box 210, Folder 1258)
    - EO 8912 - Harvard University - Symposium on Urban Minority Economic Development, 1988-1990 (Box 210, Folder 1259)
    - EO 8914 - Southern Coalition For Educational Equity - Retention and Increase of Minority Educators, 1988-1992 (Box 211, Folder 1260)
    - EO 8916 - National Urban Coalition - Economic Development Exchange, 1983-1992 (Box 211, Folder 1261-1263, Box 212, Folder 1264-1268, Box 213, Folder 1269-1270)
      Name changed from Economic Development Exchange to Community Information Exchange
    - EO 8916 - National Urban Coalition - Economic Development Exchange: Supplementary Material (Box 213, Folder 1271-1272)
    - EO 8918 - University of California, Berkeley - Local Government and Persistent Poverty Conference, 1987-1992 (Box 213, Folder 1273)
    - EO 8920 - National Conference of Black Mayors - Annual Conference, 1989, 1992; 1992 (Box 214, Folder 1274)